Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jeffsteele-0139768 (LinkedIn) www.theprivatbank.com (Company)

Jeff Steele

President - Specialized Industries US Region | CIBC Greater Chicago Area

Summary

Experienced bank executive with his entire career focused on providing financing to middle market companies. Through broad exposure to all aspects of loan structures, has a exemplary record in credit risk and underwriting resulting in portfolio performance / loss metrics far exceeding industry statistics. Accomplished talent in Asset Based, leveraged finance, cash flow, ESOP and LBO structured finance. Established successful industry verticals in Healthcare, Outdoor Advertising, Tax Lien and Specialty Finance

Experience

CIBC US

President of Specialized Industries October 2007 - Present (12 years 10 months) Greater Chicago Area

LaSalle Bank Group Senior Vice President 1992 - 2007 (15 years)

Boulevard Bank, N.A. Various June 1982 - April 1992 (9 years 11 months)

Began as commercial trainee and rose to Vice President. Boulevard was sold to the then FirstBank Systems - now U.S. Bank

Education

Indiana University - Kelley School of Business Bachelor's degree, Finance (1978 - 1982)

Stonier Graduate School of Banking (1988 - 1990)

Indiana University Bloomington

B.S., Finance · (1978 - 1982)